All right, full rockstar
treatment for Alexandr Wang, everyone.
All right.
So, why don't we start out uh backstage
we're saying, you know, one of the cool
ways to think about this event is like
you know, this room is actually full of
people who are just like us, but when we
were 18 or 20 or, you know, there's some
16-year-olds in this audience, you know.
Let's jump to your story. I mean, you
got it came up always really smart like
math olympiad like jump us to, you know,
the Alex of that time. Like, what were
you feeling? What were you thinking? And
what drove you down this road?
Yeah, I am
uh
Well, I grew up in New Mexico, Los
Alamos, New Mexico, um which now
Oppenheimer famous, but um
it really was the middle of nowhere and
uh
I remember I did all these math
competitions, all these um computer
science competitions, but then um
I knew I wanted to do really big things
and it was like not exactly clear how or
what the exact path to do that would be.
Um
and I had a friend who was really into
programming um and, you know, after high
school got an internship in the valley.
I think his first internship was at
Palantir. And um and he, you know, he
was kind of this um influence for me and
so after I finished uh high school, I
ended up working at Quora um here in
Silicon Valley. And then um
I worked there for a year. I took a gap
year to work there um and then I went to
MIT.
Um and this is I was 19 when I worked at
Quora, I was 18 when I went to MIT and I
was 19 when I started um Scale. And I
remember this period from like 17 to 19
it was um
uh
I felt like I was constantly changing
like
you know exactly what I want to do was
constantly changing. You know, I was
learning so much just from the people
around me and it was just like I felt
like I was drinking from the firehose
pretty constantly during that time. Um
and um I would definitely recommend you
know the two things that were really
important. One is I think working at a
company was really valuable because like
I think from the outside in you have no
idea how companies work. You have no
idea what it looks like to actually
build something. You have no idea what
it looks like to iterate on something.
You have no idea what it looks like for
groups of people to make decisions. And
so I thought that was really important.
And then going to school at MIT was
actually really important because it
just gave me a lot of um opportunity to
explore what was interesting. And so it
was at MIT that I started training my
first models and um that I like played
around with TensorFlow which had just
come out that year at MIT and where I
like ultimately came up with the idea of
Scale. And then after one year at MIT I
applied to YC.
You know, it felt like kind of like a
miracle to get in at that time. And uh
and YC was was really critical to my
entrepreneurial journey. Like I don't
think um like YC is this amazing blend
of uh you know, they're very supportive
and they obviously want you to succeed,
but they also give it to you very real
and they tell you when you're being a
dumbass um which I think is uh you know,
that's what we all need in life. So
um yeah, that was I think the story till
then I was 19 started Scale and uh the
rest is history.
I guess with uh you work with Jared
Friedman at the time and um you came in
with actually a very different idea than
what ended up becoming Scale.
Yeah, so we wanted to build um like an
AI agent funnily enough for uh for doc
for to help people like get medical
care. Um and it was like the right it
was a great example of an idea that I
think will ultimately exist. Like I
think we're even seeing it now. Like AI
agents to help people get medical care
are very real. But it was the wrong
timing.
Um and uh and we worked on it for about
a month or two before Jared pulled us
aside and were like, "Guys, this is I
don't know if this is going to go
anywhere."
Um and uh and that's exactly what we
needed to hear. And it was at that time
when like, you know, where I had studied
AI to my T. I had like trained models
and we thought we sort of went back to
the drawing board, thought deeply about
where the opportunity was, and
came up with Scale.
I guess selling data at the time, you
know, large language models were not
even had had not really come to the fore
yet. Um but self-driving cars were sort
of coming up and and computer vision
suddenly became So that was sort of the
first market. Is that right?
Yeah, so
the the story here is that like I was
when I was at MIT, I did a bunch of
projects like train train models of
various forms. And these were like, you
know, by comparison today, they're like
little toy models. And um and I remember
to train a model, uh I needed three
things. I needed a
uh GCP account, like I needed an account
on some cloud service to get compute. I
needed um the code to run to actually
train the model. And I needed data. I
needed a data set. And uh for two out of
these three things, you could just press
a button online and get them. And then
for the last one, for data, there was
like no effective way to get data for
training these training these models. Um
and so it felt incredibly obvious that
this was going to be the future, that
there was going to be a way to um
you know, press a button so to speak and
get data. And uh it was very funny
because
in the years that followed, like in the
first many years of Scale, data was very
unsexy still. Um every time we would go
out to fundraise, even though our
numbers were great and we had great
revenue, you know, VCs and investors
would always be very skeptical. They'd
be like, "Oh, I don't know if this is a
good business. Does it have longevity?
Is it durable?" Um
and uh it was really weird to me, but
you know, none of the investors had ever
trained a model. So, I guess they didn't
really get it. Um
and uh fast forward to today, you know,
we we managed to raise money, we managed
to keep going, managed to keep growing
the business, but um the very same
investors who passed on us and were um
were very dour on the potential of AI
are writing think pieces today about how
data is so critical and is one of the
biggest business opportunities um in AI.
So, uh it's very funny to see that whole
whole thing come full circle.
I mean, it seems like that's actually a
real good um
case study in first principles thinking,
right? Like, you can't start a company
by opening the pages of the Wall Street
Journal and saying, "Well, this data is
hot. Like, we're going to go work on
that." It's like, you literally couldn't
have started Scale that way. You had to
start from
uh think like simple statements
that are about the world that you know
to be true and then sort of building
something for that.
Yeah, I think the the key thing is you
need to develop conviction in a set of
beliefs that nobody else um agrees with.
Like, I think if you look at all the
most successful companies in the world,
um
they were started at a time long before
the sort of like core idea was popular.
And they work on that. They toil in
obscurity for years and years before,
you know, the the idea or the space or
the concept of the business, you know,
becomes consensus. And the only way
you're going to be successful is if
you're able to identify these truths
about the world early, long before
everyone else. And I think the like
I mean, one of the most surprising
things like, you know, Scale, we've been
working on AI for a decade. You know,
you just you can't base your business
decisions based on what everyone else is
saying around you. Like, if you go too
much with the herd, you will get
immensely confused and you will end up
nowhere. And so you have to develop your
own compass of what you think the future
is going to look like
because everyone else will just confuse
you.
It seems like one of the things you got
incredibly great at was you know, you
start with this kernel of like we
believe X and nobody else believes it,
but then the mechanics of building the
business are talking to investors and
convincing them and not letting them
demoralize you, talking to customers who
I mean should just get it and then
especially like convincing people to
come work for you.
Yeah, I think that the the
these early mechanics of building a
company like the these are things that I
think you might have some predisposition
be good at, but like
nobody is good at starting a company
when they start a company.
And
I remember talking to a lot of the
investors who I met very early on and
they you know, a lot of them would say
like oh, like you know, you just grew so
quickly and you changed so quickly and
like I didn't you know, I didn't see it
at the time. And I think that's probably
true for literally everyone who starts a
company like nobody is
nobody is good at something they've
never done before, right? And so
I think for all entrepreneurs, you start
out pretty shitty at everything and
the whole game is how do you develop
yourself to continuously improve to get
better and learn quickly.
Uh backstage we're talking about this is
actually a really lucky time to start a
company cuz you know, obviously you can
come do YC, uh you're you know, the
people in this room have each other,
which is kind of wild, but not only
that, now you have
a ideal personal AI that's going to tell
you, you know, hey, these are some ways
to do it. Um
Do you think that would have helped you
like accelerate even faster? Like you
know, talk
What do you think it's like to start a
company today with with AI in the age of
AI?
Yeah.
I mean I really think I think we're at
this like in amazing moment in the world
where the bottleneck is not the progress
of the AI models, the bottleneck is
diffusing that through the rest of the
world and and helping the world adapt to
this amazing technology that already
exists. Like I think if the models
didn't improve at all from today, there
would still be like decades and decades
of like total upheaval and change in the
economy and how the world operates and
and everything around us and um you
know, so I think it's as a result, it's
like one of the most incredible it's
probably a like once in a civilization
opportunity to be a dreamer and to have
a vision and to have ambition and to
impose a view of how the future world
should look by building something
amazing. Um you know, one of the things
that we were we were chatting about um
uh
you know, backstage is you know, when
when I started Scale or you know, 10
years ago, if you start a company, you
had to be um you know, it was like David
versus Goliath and you had to be clever
and you had to find like an angle into
the market and you had to sort of like,
you know, figure out um a way to compete
even though you had much fewer
resources. And now I actually think with
the power of agents um and AI broadly
speaking, it's much closer to Goliath
versus Goliath. Like I think but maybe
the startup is like a mecha Goliath that
is like vastly enhanced by the power of
agents and AI and you know, the the
large companies are the sort of like
more traditional Goliath, so to speak.
But I think that startups now like if
you properly embrace AI agents and um
figure out the way to leverage their
strengths in the most like ambitious
ways, you can easily outcompete
incumbents.
So, let's talk about super intelligence
because that's clearly that's even in
the name of your lab.
Um,
what does super intelligence mean
operationally inside Meta right now?
Yeah, I think that you know, we a year
ago Mark wrote this um,
memo about personal super intelligence,
which I think actually is very similar
to your concept of personal AGI. But,
you know, we believe that everybody in
the world, you know, all the billions of
people in the world are going to have a
super intelligence that is adapted and
tailored to them, that is enables them
to accomplish their goals, knows their
context, and ultimately is an expander
of their own agency. Like I think the
thing that we think a lot about is is
agency expansion. How do we help people
accomplish things that they couldn't
have ever dreamed of before? And what
would everyone in the world do if
everything was just easy? Um, and we
think about this in a in an ecosystem
way um, as well. I think uh, you know,
Patrick mentioned it, but you know, we
don't believe in this totalizing, you
know, totalitarian view of, you know,
AIs that control the world. We believe
that these are going to enhance this
very broad ecosystem. And so, you know,
we believe in billions of people all
around the world all having their own
personal super intelligence. And we also
believe in, you know, an explosion of
entrepreneurship. There's 200 million
businesses that uh, are on Meta's
platforms today. We think that number
should go to billions with this
explosion of of creativity and using AI
tools. And ultimately we think that, you
know, it's going to be this like dynamic
ecosystem of business agents working
with, you know, personal agents and
developing this sort of like
uh, complex ecosystem that is fully AI
supercharged.
So, I was really psyched to see Meta
Spark uh, 1.1. My my open claw
absolutely loved it. Um,
how you know, how how has running a
frontier lab been? Um, you know, the
Muse Spark level is sort of the opus
level. Uh, what's coming down the pipe?
And also I think that you're uh, you're
increasingly looking at open source
which uh, I think this audience really
loves.
Yeah, yeah.
So, I think it was um, it's been you
know, I've been at Meta for about a year
now and it's been um,
quite a year. I think uh,
you know, getting in and um, you know,
Meta we we've talked about it publicly
like Llama 4 wasn't on the trajectory
that was needed for um, for Meta and so
I got in there and we kind of did a
zero-based build of how do you um,
you know, build an entire frontier lab
uh,
you know, in some ways kind of from
scratch obviously using a lot of what we
had um, and move as quickly as possible.
And so within nine months of that moment
we launched Muse Spark 1 and then uh, two
months later we launched Muse Image and
Muse Spark 1.1 and um,
you know, there's a few things that I
think have really struck me about this.
It you know, the first is talent density
was incredibly important. That was the
the core thing to bet on and um,
like talent density is something that
compounds naturally. Like the more
talented people you have the more of the
most most talented people want to join
you. Um,
you know, in and I think it's it's kind
of um, amazing to see on the inside but
you know,
frontier AI work is research. Like we
are it is scientific work. We're
exploring what can you do with these
models? How can you push these models?
What is the what are the reaches of what
can be accomplished with these models
which requires a totally different
mindset and operating model than you
know, existed for internet companies or
internet products and what not. There's
a lot more about experimentation, about
science, about scaling and everything
ultimately is about how do you develop
a lab, an operating model, a system that
will just um, be able to compound with
all of the exponential growth that will
happen in the ecosystem. Both the
exponential growth in capabilities, the
exponential growth in compute, um, the
exponential growth in adoption and
usage. Like these are all um, we are on
this like very, very steep exponent
across maybe every dimension of the
ecosystem. And um, it's important to
develop like a like an organism. That's
how I think about the lab that that's
able to sort of grow with that. Um, you
know, it's been it's been very exciting
and we're we're going to be shipping a
lot more. So, um, I think uh, you know,
we will we just launched Muse Spark 1.1,
which was a great model. We're going to
continue to have updates on the Muse
Spark line. Um, we're also have bigger
models on the way that I think will be
uh, much more competitive with even the
very best models that are out there
today. We're going to be launching a
harness um, soon and have been working
on a harness to help empower all the
developers and agentic developers out
there. Um,
and uh, and then we're also um, you
know, as you mentioned, we're working on
open-source models. And we want to kind
of as I described before, like, we
believe in a decentralized world of AI
capability and progress and development.
Like, we want to we want to empower the
broader ecosystem and everyone in the
world to be able to build and develop
using this technology. And so, um, we
have a lot of exciting things on the way
and I think we want to be um,
we want to empower the ecosystem and
developers as much as humanly possible.
I mean, it sounds like one of the ways,
I mean, certainly when I was using uh,
Muse Spark with my Open Claw, like, it
it became clear that it was as good as
Opus, especially for that sort of
agentic flow with skill files, but it
was like eight x cheaper, actually.
Yes. Well, we I think this this goes to
it. Like, I don't, you know, we don't
believe in a world where these models
are so expensive that, you know, they
get rationed only for the most wealthy
of developers and and companies. Um,
it's important for everyone to be able
to use the technology to um, and to
build whatever they want to build with
it. And I think that, you know, we take
a view
I think the best AI products haven't
even been developed yet. You know, that
if you look at the AI ecosystem and
everything that's happened, like every
wave is 10 times bigger than the past
wave. So, you know, when I started
scale, the first wave was maybe
self-driving cars. Self-driving cars are
really awesome. They're like really,
really cool, but that was like pales in
comparison to large language models and
chatbots. And like, you know, chatbots
became this thing that was like probably
10 times bigger even than um than uh you
know, self-driving cars. And then there
were coding agents which came a few
years later. And coding agents are
probably 10 times bigger than than um
chatbots. And I think we're just on this
steep curve. Like, we're going to keep
seeing these new modalities and form
factors and developments of the AI
paradigm that will each be dramatically
bigger than the last. And so, um you
know, our point of view is like, let's
let's unleash the ecosystem. Let's
explore and let's see um let's build,
you know, kind of the future of the
world together.
So, what's the best way to actually take
advantage of the coding model uh from Muse
Spark? It's it's open code, right?
Yeah. Today, um the the easiest way is
to use open code. We have like
onboarding on the website. And then uh
soon we'll have a harness of our own.
And um ultimately, I think we want great
models that plug into all of the
available harnesses and empower as much,
you know,
uh sort of combinatorial innovation in
the ecosystem as possible.
Yeah, I know the harness is uh you know,
under wraps still. But like, can you
tease us with
you know, I mean, I still use open claw.
I still use Hermes agent. You know, it's
uh you know, these things are I call
them Ferraris that break down on the
side of the road all the time. Like, is
this a Ferrari that won't break down?
Like, you know, tease us a little bit.
Yeah, hopefully hopefully it doesn't it
doesn't break down. I mean, I think
we're really focused on speed. I think
speed is
um
you know, for anyone that uses these
tools, speed is probably the you know,
one of the most critical things. I think
also reliability, like you mentioned, we
want to be extremely reliable. Um we
want to be very extensible and to scale
to as complex and interesting of a
multi-agent setup that you that you want
to have. Like I think there's so much
innovation that will occur even above
the harness, frankly, um in terms of
like how to orchestrate and set up loops
and and develop like, you know, very
complex ecosystems of these agents
working together.
Um Uh we want to be really extensible
and and um ultimately we want to just
empower people to harness this
technology because harness that Oh,
uh no pun actually pun not intended, but
um
but there's like I truly believe these
these models are already just incredibly
powerful. Like they should they should
be so powerful to fuel, you know, um
many many points of expansion of GDP
growth and I think it's like up to smart
people with vision and ambition to make
all that happen.
Let's see. So, one question. I mean,
when you look back on the decade, um
what do you think they'll say was
obvious in hindsight about AI that
people are just missing in real time
right now?
You know, so much of the debate that
happens these days is around oh, how
good are the models actually getting and
can the models actually bridge this
issue and, you know, when are we going
to get super intelligence? Is that in
like 2 years or 5 years? And, you know,
are we going to hit a wall? And, you
know, so much of that debate is like
I think um in some ways uh
a little bit of a waste of time because,
you know,
I think it's inevitable that we're going
to have very powerful models and um you
know, rather than
I think we'll look back and say, "Oh,
all this arguing around like when
exactly it was going to happen was sort
of um was short-sighted because the
reality is we are just as a entire human
civilization on this incredible
exponential. Like you cannot look at the
progress of AI over the past decade and
not just be totally awestruck by how far
it's come. Like a decade ago, the best
AI models could recognize cats in
YouTube videos. And now, you know, we're
talking to
um you know, a digital god that can, you
know,
uh I mean, we've all seen some of the
hacks and some of the some of the things
these systems are capable of. And
you just can't help but be awestruck.
And and I think this trend will just
continue. Like these these models are
going to become more and more powerful.
And so,
I think a decade looking back, it'll
it'll be obvious that intelligence
became abundant and that agency became
abundant. Like the current trends we're
on are just going to keep continuing.
And um this will be very strange. I
mean, I think for the history of
humanity, um
you know, groups of smart people getting
together towards a shared goal was was
the bottleneck of progress. You know, US
The United States of America in some
sense was an example of this. Like the
United States of America was formed from
a smart group of very smart people
getting together and having a vision for
the future that they wanted to enact.
And that's the story of nearly every
company um in America. And it's the
story of every YC company. Um
and
that's going to change. Like all of a
sudden, the scarce resource isn't going
to be intelligence or agency. I really
think it's going to be vision and
ambition. It's like, do you have a clear
view of
what you want the world to look like in
the future? What is the like one way in
which you want to put your finger on the
scale for how the future of the world
will develop and how the how the world
will look like in 5 to 10 years that it
does not look like today? And do you
have the ambition and drive to like go
through all the crap to make that
happen? And AI will make that easier.
Like agents in AI makes that maybe 10
times or 100 times easier than it was a
decade ago. But the flip side of that is
then you all of a sudden you can dream
bigger. Like I think And the world is
like
um you know, there's so many things that
need to evolve for us to be able to
fully embrace this technology. Um you
know, the world is like really just, you
know, barely even ready for this
technology today. And I think, you know,
as a builder, we have a responsibility
to prepare the world, right? Like we
have to help enterprises and
governments, you know, to adapt to this
new technology. We have to help figure
out how we secure the world from a
biosecurity perspective or cybersecurity
perspective. We have to figure out how
we um how we're going to to manage all
these risks that we see with this new
technology. But on the flip side, it's
also the time of like, you know,
unprecedented opportunity for humans.
Like we can develop new sciences. We can
solve problems in health and biology
that have been forever unsolved. We can
build new businesses that you couldn't
have even imagined before. There's like
new creative opportunities that couldn't
have existed before. So, it's like
it's just this incredible cradle of of
opportunity and risks that uh that I
think makes it like no better time to be
someone who's a builder and um
and has a strong view of how the world
should change.
Do you think the path has changed? I
mean, one of the things I saw, I think
Stanford uh the amount of computer
science majors actually dropped by some
double-digit percentage. It's people
sort of worried like, which is sort of
insane to me. Like you still sort of
need those skills to even create agents
that are that good. Maybe that won't be
true. I'm not really sure.
How you know, have you changed you know,
what do you what would you say to people
in this audience right now? Like this is
sort of a real question that people are
sort of facing. Like should they become
more word cell and less shape rotator?
Like what you know, what's the move? And
you
has that changed um
the kind of people you're looking to
hire and, you know, how you manage your
teams right now at Meta?
I think systematic and rigorous thinking
are still incredibly important because
you know, the abstraction layer, I mean,
I didn't used to believe that this is
how it was going to play out, but it
really has, like, the abstraction layer
just keeps changing. So, you know, when
I started a company back in my day, we
wrote code. Um
And now, you know, I'm sure nobody here
writes code anymore. That's ridiculous.
But um but now it's about how do you
orchestrate the agents together? And
then it's like, how do you develop these
organizations of agents? Like, how do
you get like a million agents to work
together well? And then it'll be, how do
you get like a trillion agents to work
together well? Like, I think that
there's going to be this continued um
uh need to figure out how you structure
uh workflows at the abstraction layer
that we're going to be operating at. And
that form of like rigorous systematic
thinking, I mean, traditionally the way
this would work like in my era of
starting companies is you would start by
writing code, and then you would have
organizations of humans, and you'd
figure out how you how to organize those
humans. Um and that requires systems
thinking. And now, maybe it's like much
more much closer to first you you
orchestrate the agent, then you figure
out how to orchestrate like these armies
of agents. But um
but I think systems thinking is never
going to go out of style. So, I think
it's definitely a mistake to go all in
on Word Cell. Like, I think you need to
you need to shape rotate. Um
but then I think the sort of like um
much more of I think what's necessary
going in the future is having um
a deeper sort of compass and
philosophical view on how the world
should develop. Because I think there
are there are many many lessons um from
human history around um
how how we think civilization go through
this period. And um
So, you know, humanity will change more
in the next decade than it has in the
past 100 years, probably. And um
And so, I think like the imperative for
us to have positive visions for that and
have coherent uh articulations of how
that should develop are are more
important than ever.
Um
Let's get a little more concrete. I
mean, one of the things I'm curious
about is like, are there sort of
applications of AI that you're seeing
among your friends or internal to Meta
that you can talk about that are, you
know, they're sort of obvious near-term
maybe people haven't figured out yet. I
mean, give us some alpha.
Um, I mean,
I think there's still just like
astronomical opportunity in
uh agentic looping and and figuring out
how you develop systems that enable you
to spend like 1,000 x more or 1 million
x more on tokens to drive an outcome in
a in a continuous feedback loop. Like if
you think about most companies,
companies are just these like
large-scale feedback loops where humans
are operating each of the edges. Like,
you know, companies they um, they get
customers and they figure out to make
those customers happier. And if
customers are happier, then they spend
more. And if they spend more, then they
can hire more people who can then go
figure out how to get more customers and
make those customers happier. And that's
like this, you know, that in some sense
is the feedback loop of uh
of every startup or every business. And,
you know, these within that there are
micro feedback loops that exist. And I
think developing agentic systems that
can operate and optimize these feedback
loops is there's like just huge amounts
of of alpha there. Like I think we've
seen internally at Meta um
cases where if you can develop the right
agentic loop and you have the right eval
or the right metric for the agents to
optimize, you can have a swarm of agents
accomplish more than like a team of 100
engineers in, you know, uh
very very handily actually, very very
easily. And so, I think figuring out
what the world
um looks like with lots of uh
sort of this like um
these agentic coordination problems, I
think that is like one of the most
interesting problems today. So,
mechanically speaking, I mean, markdown
files, cron jobs, is I mean, is it
that's and then basically pointing the
agent at enough data so that it can
figure something out that, you know,
maybe isn't in distribution.
Yeah, I think figuring out Yeah, yeah,
mechanically figuring out what the
metric is and then yeah, it just comes
down to skills, markdown files, cron
jobs,
/goal.
Yeah, /goal. Like I think I think it's
always funny how mundane everything is
once you really dig into it. But um
So it's not magic, you know what I mean?
Some some people put a lot of magic
There's like some LinkedIn threads about
some magic stuff.
advice, ignore LinkedIn.
LinkedIn is where you get customers.
So I like to end on this, which is um
you know,
you get a telegram to send to the
18-year-old version of yourself, you
know, what do you say to that person
right now given all, you know, I mean,
thank you for coming back and sharing
your wisdom with this audience. I mean,
you know, what would you send in a
message in a bottle to the 18-year-old
version of yourself right now?
Yeah, I think the
I think it really boils down to
develop your own internal compass for
how you think the future will develop
and have strong conviction in it
because, you know, you will get so you
will get inundated with noise and people
telling you and like you'll could
be very confusing and it'll be very
hard. And especially when you're young
and you don't have experience like it
can feel very difficult to
um
have true conviction in what you believe
and and what you want to do. But I think
that's the most important thing. Kind of
as we talked about, you know, um
it took a deep deep conviction in what
we were building to be able to weather
the the sort of storms of many years of
um of
uh chaos in the market, in the industry,
in the people around us. And so
um And and then the other piece of
advice I would have is try to identify
what is the what is the exponential in
the world that has both the steepest
curve and will go the longest. And you
know many decades ago this curve was
was Moore's law and that probably was
you know that was
at the time like clearly the right thing
to invest on. I think right now it's AI
progress but there will be more of these
very steep curves in the future and it's
fine if these curves start
you know the starting point is very
boring or like it doesn't even seem that
interesting. Like it you know when we
started
when I started working on scale
you know we had cat detectors in YouTube
videos and that felt you know
it's hard to say explain the story that
that's like the most important
technology of our time but it was on
just this like unbelievable exponential.
Um
And I think I have one last thing I got
to say yes which is
we are meta is proud to offer everyone
in this room a thousand dollars of free
credits for the Muse Spark API.
Fantastic.
And uh
And we're going to keep making the
models better and right now Muse Spark is
I think eight x cheaper than Opus so
so if you convert that to Opus dollars
uh
it's a lot more but no everyone here
will will work to get everyone the
details on how to get how to get these
credits and we're really excited to see
what everyone builds.
Alexandr Wang everyone.